sisterjane.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy – Sister Jane

We are committed to respecting your privacy and complying with laws and regulations to ensure that the personal information you give us is kept secure and processed fairly. 

This Privacy & Cookies Policy covers how Sister Jane and our brand Ghospell (collectively, "Sister Jane", "we", "us" and "our") collect, use, and process personal information about you in connection with your relationship with us as a customer or potential customer. It is important that you read and understand the below and agree that you do not object to us using your personal information for any of the purposes outlined in this Privacy & Cookie Policy.

Sister Jane UK Limited is a company registered in England and Wales under company number 7529595

### How we collect your personal information

We may collect your personal information through one of the following ways:

  * When you visit and use our websites (the “sites”)
  * When you visit our store
  * When you interact with our digital content or sign up to our newsletters
  * When you contact our customer services team by telephone or email
  * or when you complete any forms for transactional, employment and other purposes.

### What information do we collect?

In addition to personal details such as your name, email, telephone number, address and payment details, Sister Jane may also collect some of the following personal information about you:

  * Details of transactions you make from Sister Jane (in-store or via the sites)
  * Details of shopping preferences, such as favourite products
  * Details of your visits to our sites
  * Details of when you contact our customer services team by email, phone or live chat from our Sites
  * Other information from which we can identify you.

### How do we use your information?

We will treat your information as private and confidential (but we reserve the right to disclose this information in certain circumstances, as set out below). Your personal information can be used in any of the following ways:

  1. Process and fulfil any orders you make via the sites or in-store (please note that your details may need to be passed to a third party in order for them to deliver the product you ordered and we may retain your details for a reasonable period of time after you have completed the transaction, in order to fulfil any contractual obligations, such as refunds, guarantees, etc).
  2. To process payments and prevent fraudulent transactions (we may retain your details of these purposes for a reasonable period of time and we may pass your details to a third party to carry out these functions).
  3. With your consent, we will retain your personal information, preferences and details of your transactions in order to keep you informed by email, post, and/or through other digital means including social media platforms, about products and services (including special offers, discounts, promotions, events, competitions and so on) offered by Sister Jane.
  4. To register you on the sites or in-store and where this involves setting you up with an account, we will use your personal information to maintain and update your account (e.g. such as a change of address or change in your push notification preferences).
  5. To improve the content and appearance of the sites, to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you.
  6. To assess and process your job application (we may retain a record of your information for a reasonable period of time following the end of our recruitment selection process for administration purposes).
  7. To administer any prize draws or competitions run by Sister Jane. Please refer to the specific terms & conditions for each prize draw or competition.

### Who we share your information with

In certain circumstances, as mentioned above, we may share your personal information with carefully-selected third parties, who are engaged to help us run, manage and improve the quality of the products and services that we offer, as well as for marketing and fraud and credit checking purposes, and/or to protect and defend the rights and property of Sister Jane. We only provide these companies with the information which they need to carry out their services, and they will not be permitted to use the information for other purposes. We require all third parties to treat your personal information as carefully and confidentially as we do.

You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any other regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your personal information or any other information we obtain about you, we are entitled do so.

Payments using our sites are made through our payment solutions provider, Shopify, Worldpay, First Data and Paypal. You will be providing credit or debit card information direct to our provider who process payment details further.

The personal information that you provide through the sites is processed in the United Kingdom and is stored on servers internationally, including but not limited to: USA, Canada, Australia, New Zealand and EEA.

We may transfer information that we collect from you to our sister company Ghospell, other companies who promote and sell Sister Jane products and to selected service providers who perform functions on our behalf (each as described above), based in countries outside of the U.K. and the European Economic Area ("EEA") or your country of residence. This information may be stored and processed in such countries.

Personal information stored in another jurisdiction may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in that jurisdiction according to its laws. Whether the personal information you provide to us is processed by us or our Affiliated Companies or services providers within the U.K. or EEA or outside of it, we will take steps to ensure that your personal information will be afforded the level of protection required of us under and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable data protection laws and in accordance with current legally recognised data transfer mechanisms, such as a valid Privacy Shield certification (in the case of a data transfer to a Privacy Shield certified US recipient – https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome) or appropriate EC approved standard contractual clauses (see http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/international-transfers/transfer/index_en.htm)

### Children's Privacy

You must be at least 13 years old to use our sites. If you are under 13 or a minor in your country or state of residence, your parent or legal guardian must provide their information and agree to this Privacy Policy on your behalf and you may only access and use our sites with permission from them. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 or equivalent minimum age, if we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from one, we will delete such information from our records.

### Your data protection rights

You have the right to request a copy of, amend, limit or delete the personal information we hold about you. You may do this by sending an email to hello@sisterjane.com indicating the reason for this request. Please note that we may require you to verify your identity before allowing you to access your personal information.

We will generally only keep your information as long as you remain an active customer and for 5 years afterwards, or otherwise as required for our business operations or by applicable laws. We may need to retain certain personal information even once a customer account has been closed or deleted to enforce our terms, to identify, issue or resolve legal claims, for fraud prevention and/or for proper record keeping purposes. We may also retain a record of any stated objection by you to receiving Sister Jane updates for the purpose of ensuring we can continue to respect your wishes and not contact you further. Your personal information will be deleted or destroyed in a manner that cannot be restored or reproduced.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter just email us at hello@sisterjane.comor follow the instructions about how to unsubscribe, available in all our newsletters. Alternatively, you can contact our Customer Services Team on [(+44) 20 7148 0791](tel:+44-20-7148-0791).

### Third party links

We may from time to time include third party links on our sites. These sites have separate and independent privacy policies, which we encourage you to review when you visit those sites. This Privacy Policy Statement only covers our sites and does not cover any other websites. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the privacy practices, data collected or the content of these sites.

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information, which are issued to your computer when you visit a website, storing, and sometimes tracking, information about your use of the sites. We use cookies to elevate your user experience and the quality of our sites and service. When you enter our sites our web server sends a cookie to your computer which allows us to recognise it. By associating the identification numbers in the cookies with other customer information when, for example, you log-in to the sites, we know that the cookie information relates to you.

Local storage is technology which allows a website or an app to store and retrieve data on your mobile phone or other device. We use local storage to enable certain features, including to store certain parts of our sites on your device, so that those pages load more quickly when you next visit them.

You can set your browser to reject cookies or you can delete them yourself if you wish, however, please by aware that restricting cookies and/or local storage will impact on your user experience and may prevent you from using part of our sites. You can also control the use of local storage using your browser settings.

By proceeding beyond this page, you consent to our cookie and local storage settings and agree that you understand this Policy. For more information on how to enable or disable cookies [click here.](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en)

### Cookies at SisterJane.com

#### Strictly Necessary Site Cookies

These cookies are used by our online shop platform, Shopify. They track visits to the shop and allow you to use essential features of our sites, such as processing orders and collecting payments. If we did not use these cookies you would be unable to use our sites for shopping, only for browsing.

  * _landing_page
  * _shopify_fs
  * _shopify_uniq
  * _shopify_y
  * _orig_referrer
  * cart_sig
  * secure_customer_sig
  * _y
  * checkout_token
  * cp_sessionid
  * currency
  * newsletter-newsletter-popup
  * tracked_start_checkout
  * Local storage
  * __cfduid
  * csrftoken

#### Analytical Cookies

These are common performance cookies that many websites use. They collect information about how you use our sites, so that we can elevate your user experience and improve the quality of our sites and service. All information collected is anonymous, and we will not share this information with third parties.

  * _ga
  * _gac_UA-25249804-1
  * _gat
  * _gid

#### Marketing Cookies

These cookies allow us to offer you a customised browsing experience, by providing you with interest based services both on this sites and on some other websites too.

  * MCPopupClosed
  * __unam
  * _privy_23F71C3618A04FB0D03C4469
  * _privy_a
  * fsb_previous_pathname
  * fsb_total_price_145328
  * mailmunch_second_pageview
  * marketify_browser_id
  * marketify_cart
  * marketify_country_code
  * marketify_ip_address
  * qab_previous_pathname
  * fr
  * rur
  * tr
  * urlgen
  * collect

### Changes to this privacy policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. The amended Privacy Policy will be posted on the sites so please check this page regularly for changes.

### Contacting Sister Jane

You can contact us if you have any questions regarding this policy or the use of your data at [hello@sisterjane.com](mailto:hello@sisterjane.com) or on [(+44) 20 7148 0791.](tel:+44-20-7148-0791)
